Hello, my name is Andrea Fitzer.
I am studying marketing at the University of Texas at Dallas.
I am a member of the American Marketing Association
and Alpha Kappa's side, both of which
are dedicated to shaping future business leaders.
I hope to incorporate my business knowledge
into consumer trend analysis and strengthening relationships
among consumers, as well as other companies.
I am savvy, social, and principled,
and have exquisite interpersonal communication skills.
I know that I can be an asset in any company
and or situation, and I hope that you'll consider me
for an internship or job opportunity.
Thank you so much.